Hey, Ross.
嘿，羅斯
I'm so glad someone's here. Could you zip me up?
真高興有人在這裡 你可以幫我把拉鏈拉起來嗎？
- Sure. - Thank you.
-當然可以 -謝謝
Can you believe no one between my apartment and here..
你相信從我家到這裡的路上…
offered to do that for me?
竟然沒有人願意幫我拉拉鏈嗎？
People.
真是的
So why are you so dressed up?
你穿這麼漂亮做什麼呢？
Mike's picking me up for a date.
麥克要來接我去約會
How's that going? Is it getting serious?
交往得如何呢？ 是不是越來越認真了？
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I like him.
我不知道，我不知道 我是蠻喜歡他的
But am I ready to take my Grade A loins off the meat market?
但是我還沒有準備好要退出江湖
I'm not quite sure.
我不太確定
You know, I really admire your whole dating attitude.
我真的很欣賞你的約會態度
It's so healthy. I'm always like, "Is this moving too fast?
真是很健康的態度 我總是在想會不會進展太快了？…
Is this moving too slow? Where's this going?"
會不會進展太慢了？ 這將怎麼發展呢？
I know. You are a bit of a drama queen.
我知道 你就像是個戲劇女王
You're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun..
你真是太厲害了 男朋友一個接著一個 享受樂趣...
and not worrying that it never turns into anything serious.
完全不擔心沒有結局
I wouldn't say "never."
我不敢說「完全不」
You know, there is that guy.
有一次有個男的…
Okay, well, what about..?
好的，哪個…？
Okay, there's gotta be someone.
總該有個人吧
- There isn't! That's what I'm saying. - Oh, my God, you're right!
-根本就沒有！我就說吧 -喔，天啊，你說的沒錯！
I know. And yet, here you are, all ready for the next date.
我知道，一段戀情才剛結束 馬上又可以跟其他人約會
I can't believe I never realized this before.
真不敢相信 我之前都沒有注意到這點
I'm in my 30s, and I've never been in a long-term relationship.
我已經三十幾歲了 從來沒有愛情長跑過
Oh, my God, what's wrong with me?
喔，天啊，我是有什麼毛病？
There's nothing wrong with you.
你沒有什麼毛病
I mean, you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married.
我是說，你不像那種 看起來會想結婚的人
I want to get married!
我想結婚！
No, please.. Please don't cry because of me.
別這樣，拜託…別因為我而哭
I don't know what I'm talking about, okay? I've been divorced three times.
我根本不知道我在說什麼 我離婚三次了
At least you've been married.
至少你結過婚
Oh, my God! I want to trade lives with Ross?!
喔，我的天啊！ 我竟然羨慕起羅斯了？
Phoebe.
菲比
- What's wrong? - Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
-怎麼了？ -沒事，要跟你約會太興奮了
Mike, this is Ross Geller. Ross, this is Mike..
麥克，這位是羅斯蓋勒 羅斯，這位是麥克…
- Sorry, I didn't catch that. - Mike Hanigan.
-對不起，我沒有聽清楚 -麥克漢尼根
- Ross Geller. - Hey.
-羅斯蓋勒 -嘿
So are you sure you're ready to go?
你確定準備好了嗎？
How do I look?
我看起來怎樣？
- Do you have a compact in your purse? - No.
-你皮包裡有小鏡子嗎？ -沒有
You look great.
你看起來棒透了
The One With The Sharks
本集播出：鯊魚
rianystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Hey, Joey. - This girl won't turn around.
-嘿，喬伊 -那個女的就是不轉過來
I can't tell if she's hot or not. What do you think?
我無法判斷她是不是很辣 你覺得呢？
Joey, I am not going to objectify women with you.
喬伊，我不會跟你一起把女性物化的
But if her face is as nice as her ass..
但是如果她的臉 跟她的屁股一樣棒的話…
- Mama! - All right. Thanks.
-媽媽咪啊！ -好的，謝謝
- Have you talked to Chandler? - He has to stay in Tulsa this weekend.
-你有跟錢德講電話了嗎？ -他這週末要留在土爾沙
- How come? - I don't know. He has to work.
-為什麼？ -我不知道，有工作要做
There's some big rush on the..
要趕那個…
Damn it. I'm gonna have to start listening when he talks about his job.
討厭！我應該要開始 認真聽他講工作的事了
Why don't you fly out there and surprise him?
你何不飛過去給他個驚喜呢？
I'd love to. I really miss him.
我很想啊，我真的很想念他
But I can't. I have one day off and it's just too expensive.
但是不行，我只有放一天假 而且機票太貴了
Interesting. So Chandler's not worth the price of a plane ticket to you.
真好玩，所以機票錢 比錢德還重要
Of course he is.
當然是錢德較重要
Maybe I will go.
或許我應該飛過去
We'll have a little second honeymoon at the Tulsa Ramada.
我們可以在土爾沙的飯店 來個二度小蜜月
You should bring your black see-through teddy with the attached garters.
你應該帶你那件黑色透明性感內衣 加上吊帶褲襪
- How do you know I have one of those? - Didn't until just now.
-你怎麼知道我有那件呢？ -本來不知道，現在知道了
Hot. Not hot.
辣，不辣
Hot!
辣！
Excuse me?
什麼？
I said that I think you're hot.
我說我覺得你很辣
And.. now I'm embarrassed.
而…現在我糗死了
I thought you said "hi."
我以為你是說「嗨」
That would've been better.
如果是那樣就好了
I'll try that. Hi, I'm Joey.
我來試試看，嗨，我是喬伊
I'm Hayley.
我是海莉
Look, I don't normally ask out women that I meet in coffeehouses.
通常我不約在咖啡店遇到的女生出去
Gesundheit.
保重
But..
但是…
This is hard. I'm kind of shy.
真是很難開口，我有點害羞
Seriously, you should see someone about that cold.
真的，你應該去看醫生的
If it gets much worse, you could die.
如果感冒越來越嚴重，你可是會死的
- Anyway.. - I would love to go out with you.
-反正… -我很樂意跟你出去
Really? Great.
真的嗎？太棒了
Did I..? Did I actually ask you?
我有…我有開口約你嗎？
That's just where you were going. I figured I'd help you out.
由你說話的方式 我就猜得到你要做什麼
You don't seem like the kind of guy who does this a lot?
你不像是那種經常這樣的男生吧？
Damn it, Gunther, you gave it to me.
真是的，阿甘，你傳染給我了
Oh, it's you.
喔，是你
With vegetarian corndogs.
我帶了素食熱狗
Come on, I just want to talk to you.
別這樣，我只想跟你說說話
About what? How few ova I have left?
說什麼？說我還剩下幾個卵子嗎？
Come on, I just wanna apologize for what happened yesterday.
別這樣，我只想為昨天發生的事道歉
I'm sorry, Phoebe.
我很抱歉，菲比
That's okay, Ross.
沒關係，羅斯
- So how'd the date go? - Well, it was awful.
-約會還好嗎？ -糟透了
I barely got through dinner.
我幾乎撐不過晚餐
Every time I thought about what you said, I cried.
每次我想到你說的話，我就哭了
I'm pretty sure he spent most of the night just staring at me in horror.
我非常肯定他整晚都驚恐的盯著我看
But I couldn't know for sure because my eyes were swollen shut.
但是我無法真的確定 因為我的眼睛已經腫到張不開了
You know I wasn't trying to make you cry.
你知道我不是故意要惹你哭的
I was really trying to say something nice.
我本來是想要說一些很好聽的話的
I was basically saying even though you've never been in a serious relationship..
我只是要說，即使你 從未有過認真的感情…
- Are we gonna do this again? - Sorry.
-我們還要再討論這個嗎？ -對不起
- So he hasn't called? - Would you call this girl:
-他還沒打來嗎？ -你會打給這種女的嗎？
"Thanks for.. a lovely.. evening"?
「謝謝…美好…一晚」
Now I feel terrible. This is all my fault.
我覺得糟透了 這全都是我的錯
You know what you should feel terrible about?
你知道更糟的是什麼嗎？
This could have been my serious guy.
這男的有可能是可以認真的對象
He was sweet and smart and funny.
他很體貼、聰明又風趣
You know how hard it is to meet a guy like that?
你知道要遇到這樣的男生有多難嗎？
We are a rare breed.
我們的確是稀有動物
Hey, maybe that's him.
嘿，可能就是他哦
Hello?
喂？
Could you hold on one sec?
你可以等一下嗎？
- I need some privacy. - Is it Mike?
-我需要一點隱私 -是不是麥克呢？
No, it's a heavy breather. I'll take what I can get.
不，是騷擾電話 我現在什麼都接了
I'm listening.
我在線上
What a great dinner.
晚餐實在太棒了
Thanks again for letting me have that last piece of cake at the restaurant.
再次謝謝你讓我吃最後一塊蛋糕
You're welcome again. I'm gonna go make some coffee.
不用客氣，我要去煮咖啡
- Can I get you anything? - Do you have any cake?
-你要什麼呢？ -你有蛋糕嗎？
So this is going pretty good.
真是進行的太順利了
Dinner was nice. We've got a lot in common.
晚餐很棒，我們有許多共同點
Victoria 's Secret.
「維多莉亞的秘密」(性感內衣目錄)
We even like the same books.
我們甚至喜歡相同的書
There's a scary painting.
這幅畫真可怕
Wait a minute.
等等
I think I've been scared by that painting before.
我記得好像被這幅畫給嚇過
You know what? This whole place looks familiar.
你知道嗎？ 這地方看起來真眼熟
I have definitely been in this apartment.
我一定曾經來過這裡
I know I've seen this weird plant before.
我看過這棵可怕的植物
It did that the last time!
它上次也是這樣刺我！
Oh, my God. I've gone out with this girl before.
喔，天啊 我跟這個女的約會過
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
沒錯！我們在這沙發上做過愛！
And then on that chair, and.. No.
然後在那張椅子上 還有…，不對
No, we didn't do it here..
不對，沒有在這裡…
which is weird, because it seems like a perfectly good place.
這倒是很奇怪，看起來超適合的
That's why.
這就是為什麼
Hey, Mike. Sorry to just drop by like this. Can I come in?
嘿，麥克，很抱歉這樣跑過來 我可以進來嗎？
Sure.
當然
Who are you?
你是誰呢？
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse?
我是羅斯，菲比在咖啡屋的朋友
I really, really need to talk to you about something.
我真的非常需要跟你談一件事
Unless..
除非…
You're not gonna try and get me to join a cult, are you?
你不是要拉我信什麼教吧？
No, it's just, you know, you have that look.
沒啦，因為，你知道的 你長得很像那種人
Damn Supercuts!
該死的199剪髮！
- Well, what's up? Is Phoebe okay? - Oh, yeah, yeah.
-怎麼回事呢？菲比還好嗎？ -喔，還好，還好
Phoebe is great. But..
菲比很好，但是…
I'm an idiot, okay?
我是個蠢蛋
Right before you guys went out..
就在你們出去約會前…
I accidentally got her all upset.
我不小心惹得她很難過
That's why she was weird.
難怪她不對勁
Yes. Yeah, I..
是的，是啊，我…
Yeah, I said something stupid about her never having had a serious relationship.
我說了些蠢話，關於她從沒有過 認真的戀愛關係等等
But you should know, she is so much fun. A wonderful person.
但是你應該知道，她是很風趣的 很棒的一個人
- Please, don't blow her off. - I'm not gonna blow her off.
-拜託，別將她判出局 -我不會判她出局的
I just spoke to her. We're going out tomorrow night.
我才剛跟她說完電話 我們明晚要出去
I mean, I hope that's okay with you, stranger from the coffeehouse.
我是說，如果你沒有意見的話 咖啡屋的陌生人
That's great. So the crying didn't turn you off?
太棒了，所以她狂哭並沒有嚇跑你？
I just got out of a nine-year relationship with a manic-depressive.
我剛剛跟一個躁鬱症患者 結束九年的戀情
Compared to that, Phoebe's a Mousketeer.
跟她相比，菲比根本是只小貓
Well, then, I didn't need to bother you.
好吧，那我就不需要再打擾你了
You or the four other Mike Hanigans I bothered.
你，外加四個麥克漢尼根 都被我打擾了
One of whom was quite large and a little flirty.
其中一個還很高壯 有點愛打情罵俏
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Is that true what you said?
等等，等等 你剛剛說的是真的嗎？
Phoebe's never had a serious relationship?
菲比從未談過認真的戀愛？
Of course she has.
她當然有過
If she's never had a serious relationship..
如果她沒有談過認真的戀愛…
do you think I'd go around broadcasting it..
你認為我會到處去廣播…
like some kind of unstoppable moron?
像是無法克制的白癡一樣 見人就說嗎？
- But you did say it. - Yes. Yes, I did.
-但是你的確是那樣說了 -是的，是的，我是說了
And I will also say..
而且我還會說…
what I'm about to say..
我接下來要說的…
vis-a-vis..
相對於…
the following.
以下的說法
Phoebe has never had a serious relationship..
菲比從未談過認真的戀愛…
since..
是從…
her super-serious relationship..
她超級認真地…
with..
跟…
Vikram.
偉軟分手之後
- Vikram? - What? That's a real name.
-偉軟？ -怎樣？那是真的名字
Stop it!
停停吧！
Why couldn't they have sent me to Texas?
為什麼不是派我去德州呢？
Seven o'clock.
七點鐘
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
或許我該去健身房
Who am I kidding? Pay-per-view porn.
少來了，還是看情色頻道好了
- Do not disturb! Do not disturb! - Surprise!
-不要打擾！不要打擾！ -驚喜吧！
- Monica? - Is everything all right?
-摩妮卡？ -一切都還好吧？
Yeah, everything's great. I was just..
是啊，一切都很好 我剛剛…
watching some regular television there.
在看一些正常的電視節目
What a pleasant surprise.
這個驚喜真是太令人興奮了
- I'm gonna go freshen up, okay? - Okay, honey.
-我去梳洗一下，好嗎？ -好的，親愛的
That was close.
差一點點
- Hello. - Hey, Rach, it's me.
-喂 -嘿，瑞秋，是我
Okay, I just got to Chandler's room, and I caught him..
我剛到錢德的房間 然後看到他…
molesting himself.
正在自摸
That couldn't have been pretty.
那劃面可能不是很好看
But you know, guys do that.
但是你知道的，男生常那樣做的
Well, the weird part is..
但是，很奇怪的是…
he was getting off.. to a shark-attack show!
他在看的是鯊魚攻擊影片耶！
- No! - Yes! Chandler watches shark porn!
-好惡！ -是的！錢德竟然在看鯊魚色情片！
- While watching sharks? - Yeah.
-在看鯊魚的時候？ -是啊
Are you sure that's what he was doing?
你確定他是在做那檔事嗎？
You know how many times I've seen him jump up like that?
你知道我看他 那樣跳起來過多少次了嗎？
Believe me, I know what he was doing.
相信我，我知道他在做什麼
Man! Sharks!
天啊！鯊魚！
I always knew there was something weird about that dude.
我就知道那個人有地方不對勁
You promised to love him no matter what.
你發誓過無論如何都要愛他的
"What" means, like, if he gets a disease or kills someone.
「無論如何」講的是像如果他得病 還是殺了人什麼的
Not if he gets his jollies to Jaws.
而不是如果 他把小弟弟放到鯊魚嘴裡
You know what, honey? Guys are just different.
你知道嗎？親愛的 男生是很不一樣的
They like things that we can't understand.
他們喜歡一些我們無法理解的東西
I once dated this guy who wanted to pretend..
我曾經約會過一個男的 總是想要假裝…
that he was an archeologist, and I was this..
他是考古學家 而我是…
naughty cavewoman who he unfroze from a block of ice.
他從冰塊中解救出來 調皮的山頂洞女人
Are you talking about my brother?
你是在說我哥嗎？
I didn't disguise that very well, did I?
我裝得不像，對不對？
- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
I went out with this girl last night. Halfway through our date I realized..
我昨晚跟一個女孩子出去 我到一半的時候才發現…
I already slept with her.
我已經跟她上過床了
You've slept with all the women in N.Y., and now you're going around again?
所以你已經跟全紐約的女人上過床了 現在只是從頭開始再來一次？
That's not even the weird part.
這還不是最奇怪的地方
- She didn't remember sleeping with me! - You don't remember sleeping with her.
-她竟然不記得跟我上過床了！ -你也不記得跟她上過床啊
But she should remember sleeping with me. I am very memorable!
但是她應該要記得的 我可是很令人難忘的！
- You guys know. - How do we know?
-你們知道的 -我們怎麼會知道呢？
- We've never slept with you. - And whose fault is that?
-我們又沒有跟你上過床 -那是誰的錯呢？
What's the big deal? You forgot, she forgot.
又沒有什麼大不了的 你忘了，她忘了
- Maybe you were having an off night. - Hey!
-或許那天晚上你沒有達陣！ -嘿！
I never have an off night. Okay?
我向來都有達陣的，好嗎？
Although, sometimes if I'm a little bloated, I don't feel that sexy.
雖然有時候如果我吃太脹 可能就不會覺得很性感
But even then, I'm better than most!
但是即使是那樣，我都比別人強！
Honey, why don't you just let it go and ask her out again?
親愛的，你何不就此釋懷 再約她出去呢？
You're both so slutty, you don't remember who you slept with.
你們都是騷貨 你們根本都不記得跟誰上過床
You're made for each other.
你們是天生的一對
Interesting.
真有趣
Well, I'll go out with her again and I'll try to get past it.
好吧，我會再跟她出去 然後忘了過去
No salt! Bloaty!
不吃鹽！會脹氣！
- Joey? - What?
-喬伊？ -幹嘛？
You don't think sharks are sexy, do you?
你會覺得鯊魚很性感嗎？
No.
不會
Wait a minute. Wait, what was the Little Mermaid?
等一下，等等 小美人魚是鯊魚嗎？
It's open!
門沒鎖！
- Hey. - Mike called! We're going out again!
-嘿 -麥克打電話來了，我們要再約會了！
Quick thing. I went to talk to Mike.
一件小事，我去找麥克談過
What?
什麼？
What did you..? What did you do, Ross?
你做…？ 你做了什麼？羅斯
Oh, boy. You got mad at that part.
喔，天啊，光這樣你就生氣了
I went over there, you know, to tell him how..
我過去找他，告訴他…
How great you are. But..
你是個很棒的人，但是…
Well, you know me. Blah-blah-blah.
嗯，你知道我的，話太多了
- And I ended up telling him that.. - What?
-然後我最後竟然告訴他… -什麼？
You had a six-year-long relationship..
你有過六年的戀情…
with a guy named Vikram.
跟一個叫做偉軟的人
What? Why?
什麼？為什麼？
Well, he seemed..
因為，他…
to bum hard when I told him you'd never been in a serious relationship.
在我說你從未談過 認真的戀情之後，好像有點驚訝
If you hadn't just had a baby with my best friend..
如果你不是剛跟我 最要好的朋友生下小孩
I swear to Lucifer..
我跟撒旦發誓…
a rabid dog would be feasting on your danglers right now!
一隻狂犬病瘋狗正要吃掉 你褲檔裡的那根東西了！
I think you'll feel differently when you know..
我想如果你知道多一點關於偉軟的事…
a little bit about Vikram.
你會感覺好多了
Okay, he's a..
好的，他是…
He's a kite designer.
他是風箏設計師
And he used to date Oprah.
而且他曾經跟於美人約會過
I'm not going along with some lie you made up, Ross.
我不會跟你唱雙簧說謊的，羅斯
- I'm just gonna be honest with him. - Good.
-我會跟他老實說 -很好
Just be honest with him.
跟他老實說
- I have nothing to be ashamed of. - No.
-我沒有什麼好隱瞞的 -沒錯
So I haven't been in a relationship that lasted longer than a month.
就算我的每段感情 都沒有超過一個月…
Okay? I haven't had a real boyfriend.
那又如何呢？是啊 我是沒有過真正的男朋友
If he can't handle it, then he can leave. Which he will.
如果他無法接受 那他可以離開，我想他會離開的
And, you know, that's okay. So I'll just be alone forever.
而這一切都沒有關係 我只不過會永遠孤單而已
You know, all right. It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
都沒關係了，一切都會沒事的
I'll go on walking tours with widows and lesbians.
我就跟寡婦還有同性戀一起出去玩嘛
- I'll get it. - Okay.
-我去開門 -好的
I'm trying to remember the last time I opened a door and you weren't there.
讓我想想有哪一次，開門的人不是你
Phoebe, are you okay?
菲比，你還好嗎？
Yeah. There's just..
還好，只不過是…
There's something you should know.
有件事你必須要知道
Vikram just called.
偉軟剛打電話來
So it was really a shock after 25 years of marriage..
所以在經歷二十五年的婚姻之後 這真是很讓人驚訝
my parents getting divorced. I took it the hardest..
我的模範父母竟然要離婚 我真的很難接受
- because I was the youngest. - Sure. Yeah.
-因為我是老么 -當然囉
How can you not remember me?
你怎麼會忘了我是誰？
What?
什麼？
How could you not remember that we slept together?
你怎麼會忘了我們上過床？
- What? When? - I don't know!
-什麼？何時？ -我不知道！
I really, really think I would remember sleeping with you.
我真的、真的認為 如果有我會記得的
Come on, come on. Search your brain, all right? It was..
快點，快點 仔細回想，好嗎？那就在…
a certain amount of time ago. I was here. You were here.
之前某個時候 我在這裡，你在這裡
We had sex here, here, here..
我們在這裡，這裡，這裡…
Not there.
沒有那裡，嘿咻
- Anything? - No, it's not ringing any bells.
-想起來了嗎？ -沒，一點印象也沒有
My God, woman!
天啊，女人！
How many people have you been with not to remember this?
你跟多少人上過床 讓你根本不記得我？
Hey, Hayley. We really gotta fix that doorknob.
嘿，海莉 我們真的要修理那個門把了
Joey?
喬伊？
I slept with you!
我跟你上過床！
And you obviously remember me! Hey, I still got it!
而且很明顯的你記得我！ 嘿，表示我還不賴！
So we're good.
所以我們還好嘛
I'll let myself out.
我自己出去
And I said, "Okay, Vikram..
然後我說，偉軟…
you can't just call every time you get lonely.
你不能每次寂寞就打電話給我
You gave up that right when you slept with Rachel."
在你跟瑞秋上床之後 你就沒有那個權力了
Rachel? I thought she just had a baby with Ross.
瑞秋？我以為她才剛生下羅斯的小孩
Yeah, well..
是啊，嗯…
Yeah.
是啊
But Emma's birth certificate might say "Geller"..
艾□的出生證明上或許生父是羅斯…
but her eyes say "Mukherjee."
但是她長得像偉軟
That is so wrong. And on top of that, he's a glue sniffer?
這實在太糟了 而且他還吸強力膠？
I know. But he calls, and my heart goes to him.
我知道，但是他打來時 我的心就飛向他了
You know, that bastard is one smooth-talking freelance kite designer.
你知道的，那個渾蛋是個很會 說話的風箏設計師
If you want, I'll mess him up for you.
如果你要的話，我可以幫你修理他
You would do that?
真的嗎？
Unless he's big. If he's really big, I'll send him..
除非他很大只 如果他真的很大只，我會給他…
a rude letter.
一封信，罵死他
I think there's somebody better out there for you.
我想有更好的人在等著你
I mean, you know, I'm.. I'm not saying me, but..
我是說，你知道的，我… 我不是指我，但是…
Maybe.. me.
或許…是我
And you don't have to worry about glue-sniffing with me.
而且你不用擔心我會吸強力膠
Although, I do smell the occasional Magic Marker.
雖然有時候我會聞馬克筆的味道
Yeah. Anyway, I just..
是啊，反正，我只是…
I think I can make you happy.
我想我可以讓你快樂
- Okay, I can't do this. - What's wrong?
-好了，我辦不到 -怎麼了？
Well, there is no Vikram. Ross made him up.
根本沒有偉軟這個人 羅斯亂扯的
Because I..
因為我…
I really never have been in a long-term relationship.
我從未有過愛情長跑
I've never lived with a guy. I've never even celebrated an anniversary.
我從未跟男人同居過 從來沒有慶祝交往一週年
So..
所以…
If that's too weird for you..
如果這對你而言太奇怪…
and you want to leave, I understand.
所以你想現在就走人 我可以理解
In fact, I'll close my eyes to make it less awkward.
事實上，我要閉上雙眼 讓這一切不至於太尷尬
You kissed me.
你親了我
- You don't think I'm a total freak? - No.
-你不認為我是怪人嗎？ -不
Well..
那麼…
Look, can I..?
那，我可不…？
Can I think you're a little weird and also cool..
我可不可以認為你有點怪 但又有點酷…
for telling me the truth and also want to kiss you?
因為你告訴我事情的真相 而且讓我想親你？
I guess so.
我想應該可以
Can I think it's cool that you kissed me..
我可不可以認為，你親我真是很酷…
and also want to kiss you again?
而且我想要親回去？
And be a little concerned about the Magic Markers?
有一點擔心馬克筆的事可以嗎？
Definitely.
當然可以
This is Vikram.
我是偉軟
I need to talk to you about the long-term relationship we had.
我需要跟你談我們之間 那段長期的戀情
Call me. I am in my kite-making studio.
回電給我，我在我的風箏工作室
Hi, honey, I'm home.
嗨，親愛的，我回來了
Hi.
嗨
- How was your flight? - It was great.
-旅途還好嗎？ -不錯
I ordered a pool float from the Sky Mall.
我從飛機上的購物目錄訂了浮板
Why'd I do that?
為什麼我要訂呢？
Why don't you sit down.
過來坐下吧
Get yourself comfortable.
放輕鬆、舒服點
Because I have a little..
因為我有個小…
surprise for you.
驚喜要給你
Well, well, well. It must be 5:00 in Tulsa..
喔，喔，喔 土爾沙現在一定是五點…
because it's "sex o'clock" in N.Y.C.!
因為紐約現在是「六」點（音近性）！
Okay. This is how much I love you.
好了，這代表我有多愛你
The great white..
大白鯊…
Honey?
親愛的？
Why am I watching a bunch of sharks swimming around?
為什麼要我看一群鯊魚游來游去呢？
Is this..? Is this not the good part?
這不是…？ 這不是你愛看的嗎？
Do you want me to fast-forward to something.. toothier?
要我快轉嗎？ 轉到露齒…比較多的地方嗎？
No, I'm just not sure that you got the right movie, that's all.
不，我只是想確定 你是不是拿錯了錄影帶
This is the only one they had at our video store.
錄影帶店裡只有這一卷
Though they did have something called Crocodile Killers.
不過他們倒是有一部叫「鱷魚殺手」的
Or does it always have to be sharks?
還是說，你非要鯊魚不可呢？
Does what always have to be sharks?
為什麼我非要鯊魚不可？
Look, we can do something else.
聽著，我們可以來點別的
Do you want me to get into the tub and.. thrash?
你要我到浴缸裡…再用力扭嗎？
- What's going on? - It's okay. It's okay.
-到底是怎麼回事？ -沒關係，沒關係的
I still love you.
我還是愛你的
- Let me be a part of this. - Let me be a part of this!
-讓我瞭解這一切 -是你應該讓我瞭解這一切！
I saw what you were doing in Tulsa.
我看到你在土爾沙做的事
Angry sharks turn you on!
憤怒的鯊魚讓你「性」奮！
No, they don't.
不，並沒有
Then why were you watching them and giving yourself a treat?
那為什麼你一邊看著他們 一邊自己玩呢？
Oh, my God! When you came in, I switched the channel.
喔，天啊！當你一進來 我就轉台了
I was just watching regular porn.
我本來只是在看一般的色情片
Really?
真的嗎？
Yes. Just some good, old-fashioned, American, girl-on-girl action.
是的，只不過是一些正常 老套、美式的女對女動作片
Can I tell you how happy that makes me?
這件事真是讓我太高興了
You are an amazing wife.
你是個不可思議的老婆
Really, you are amazing. You were actually gonna do this for me?
真的，太不可思議了 你真的願意為我這樣做？
Where do you find the strength and the understanding for that?
你是怎麼會有這樣的 意志跟諒解呢？
I'm very, very drunk right now.
因為我現在非常、非常地醉
Ordinarily, I would talk to her, but my confidence is shaken.
通常我會去跟她搭訕的 但是我的自信已經動搖了
Did I sleep with her? Did I not sleep with her?
我有跟她上床嗎？ 我沒有跟她上床嗎？
Maybe this is a wake-up call. You know, about your whole dating attitude.
或許該是你反省的時候了 檢討你的整個約會態度
You're in your 30s and you have never been in a long-term relationship.
你已經三十好幾了 沒有談過一個長期的戀愛
Here you go from woman to woman..
女人從一個換到另一個…
meaningless experience to meaningless experience.
沒有意義的關係 換到另一個沒有意義的關係
Never even worrying that it doesn't turn into something more serious.
從不擔心這些戀情都沒有任何的發展
You're right. I love my life!
你說的沒錯，我愛死我的人生了！
I actually did sleep with her.
事實上我跟她上過床了